[Music]
do it do it on shoulders it's a friendly
time it's better
to alone other a critical voice shouting
that is fine that it's not worth my time
make sure to comment your code clearly
in places it could get confusing so that
others can follow along if a programmer
can't read your code that they aren't
worthy of it Well my two hands Tu my
away left and right Voice have a say to
a said or do I
sway gentle Wings sweep on my right but
on my left to tail and Spike to work in
dark mode or in light remember if you
have a lot of Junior programmers on the
team you might need to break this
section out more to usual but how will
they learn unless you throw them in the
deep
end while both can have good points I
know I'll be busy unless I a rap B join
still a so bitter voice ins I by skull
shouts that I've already made the B far
too steady don't you know that your
supervisors will get angry if you spend
too much time on this right now look
like a hero and let someone else pick up
the pieces you know you're a team think
of your teammates you like someone else
dropping the ball on you would you I
already did you fool that's why we're
here all my two hands have my way left
and right Voice have a say do I steady
or do I
sway GLE Wing sleep on my right but on
my left to tail and Spike to work in
dark mode or in the light you know their
code works but it's ugly and you know it
maybe you should call a meeting about it
and pretend it's more important than
your current task it may be messy but
they did a very good job of decoupling
it and you know it do different tracks
of thought inside my head makes me
wonder if the Motions were my cod's been
L and my logical programmer a monkey
tapping Keys hoping that'll make magic
if I tap infinitely you're a good
programmer there's no such thing as a
good programmer just a dishonest
that's not true so let's prove her wrong
programate
[Music]
yourent left and right Voice have a say
do I setting or do I
sway gentle we sleep on my right but on
my left a tail and Spike to work in dark
mod or in light
[Music]
n